Beware of phishing attacks, Teads will never ask for your credentials on social media. Never share them. [Learn more →](https://www.teads.com/phishing-the-influencer-scam/)

Menu

Teads Website Privacy Policy
============================

Last updated: January 23, 2020

Teads SA., together with its affiliates (“Teads,” “we,” “us,” or “our”) takes your privacy very seriously. This privacy policy governs and details Teads’ data practices on how we collect, use, process, and share the data we collect through our website [www.teads.com](https://www.teads.com/) (the “Services”). This privacy policy does not describe Teads’ data practices relating to information Teads collects through its advertising services. Your use of the Site is also governed by the Terms of Use.

To access our privacy policy governing our advertising service only, please [click here](https://www.teads.com/privacy-policy/) 

As used herein, “personal data” means any information that identifies, relates to, describes, is reasonably capable of being associated with, or could reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly, with a particular Teads customer or consumer or his or her household. 

Please note that we may update or change this privacy policy. If we revise our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If we make any material changes we will notify you by means of a notice on this site prior to the change becoming effective. Please check the Teads website [www.teads.com](https://www.teads.com/) for the latest version of the privacy policy.

1\. Information We Collect
--------------------------

### Information You Provide Us. 

We collect personally identifiable information, including identifiers, such as your name, phone number, company name and email address, directly from you when you choose to enter it on our website, for instance when you complete the “Contact Us” form.

### Automatically Collected Information.

When you access or use our Services, we automatically collect information about you, including:

* **Internet and Other Electronic Network Activity Information:** We collect information related to your access to and use of the Services, as well as information about the computer or mobile device you use to access our Services, including, e.g.
    * Page URL
    * Browser information (e.g. Browser name and version)
    * Device Information (e.g. Device type, OS)
    * Network carrier information (e.g. Wi-Fi, 46 or Wired connection)
    * Mobile application information (e.g. Application name or IDFA)
    * User interactions with Teads Ad
* **Geolocation Information:**  We may derive the non-precise location of your device from your IP address. 
* **Information Collected by Cookies and Similar Tracking Technologies:** Teads and our partners use cookies and similar technologies to collect information, including cookies and web beacons. Cookies are small data files created on your device that help us improve our Services and your experience, see which areas and features of our Services are popular, and count visits.   Web beacons (also known as “pixel tags” or “clear GIFs”) are electronic images that may be used in our Services or emails and help deliver cookies, count visits, and understand usage and campaign effectiveness. You can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level, but if you choose to disable cookies, it may limit your use of certain features or functions on our website.

2\. Use of Information 
-----------------------

We use the personal information we collect for various business and commercial purposes, including those described below:

* **Providing customer service:** We use the information to respond to the request or inquiry you have submitted to us through the contact form or other entry field.
* **Marketing: We use the information for marketing purposes, such as to send you our newsletter or other promotional emails. You may choose to stop receiving our marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these communications.**
* **Debugging, identifying, and repairing errors:** We may use data to fix issues that impair the functionality of our Services.
* **Protecting the rights and property of Teads and Complying with Law:** We may use data to protect our rights and property and comply with our legal obligations, including to detect, investigate, and prevent fraud and other illegal activities and to enforce our agreements; and
* **Carry out certain short-term activities:** We may use data for other short-term, reasonable internal purposes related to our Services or your ongoing relationship with us.  

We also use cookies which are placed for the following purposes:

* **Personalization of your navigation:** We use cookies to enable us to recognize you and remember any information you have entered during your navigation on our website (such as language choice, country you are browsing from, or browser type). This makes your visit on our website easier as we don’t ask you the same information several times during your navigation.
* **Analyzing our website activity:**  We use cookies, including Hubspot and Google Analytics, to analyze trends, administer the website, and track users’ movements around our Site. These are tools that enable us to measure the performance of the navigation on our website and provide you with personalized marketing messages. For more information on the cookies used by these websites, you can refer to their specific privacy statements listed below:

3\. Sharing of Information with Third Parties
---------------------------------------------

We do not share your information with third parties for their promotional purposes. We may share information about you as follows:

* With our subsidiaries, affiliated companies, and trusted third party service providers working under the instruction of Teads, such as an email service provider, hosting provider or data center, exclusively for storage purposes. Such third parties who provide services on our behalf are authorized to use your personal information only as strictly necessary to provide these services to us.
* In response to a request for information if we believe disclosure is in accordance with, or required by, any applicable law or legal process, including lawful requests by public authorities to meet national security or law enforcement requirements;
* If we believe your actions are inconsistent with our user agreements or policies, if we believe you have violated the law, or to protect the rights, property, and safety of Teads or others;
* In connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing or acquisition of all or a portion of our business by another company; and
* With your consent or at your direction.

4\. Social Sharing Features
---------------------------

* We use communication tools to share links with social networks. If you click on these features, such as social media widgets or “share” buttons, the company providing them may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site and may place cookies when you are connected into their services. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it. For more information on the cookies used by these websites, you can refer to their specific privacy statements listed below:
    * Facebook: [http://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/](http://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/)
    * Google +: [https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/)
    * LinkedIn: [https://www.linkedin.com/legal/privacy-policy](https://www.linkedin.com/legal/privacy-policy)
    * Twitter: [https://twitter.com/privacy](https://twitter.com/privacy)

We of course remain responsible for making sure they commit themselves to adhere to this privacy policy and applicable data protection legislation by signing a data processing agreement.

5\. Additional Disclosures for Individuals in Europe
----------------------------------------------------

### Consent

The collection of personal data based on your consent is done by using a consent form as for instance on our Contact Us page. Your consent is stored and documented in our systems. You may withdraw any consent to personal data processing at any time.

### Legitimate interest

We may use your personal data if it is considered to be of legitimate interest, and if your privacy interests do not override this interest. To establish the legal basis for data collection, an assessment has been made during which a mutual interest between you and Teads has been identified. This legal basis is primarily related to our sales and marketing purposes. We will always inform you about your privacy rights and the purpose for collecting your personal data. In such cases, you can always choose to object to the processing of your personal data.

### Legal Disclaimer

We reserve the right to disclose or transfer your personally identifiable information as required by law, as part of a merger, acquisition, dissolution or sale of assets, and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process. You will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our website of any change of ownership, uses of your personal information, and choices you may have regarding your personal information.

We may also disclose your personal information when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud or respond to a government request. We may also disclose your personal information to any other third party with your prior consent.

### Access

Upon request, Teads will provide you with information about whether we hold any of your personal information. You may update, access or request deletion of your personally identifiable information by contacting us a [dpo@teads.com](mailto:dpo@teads.tv). We will respond to your request within a reasonable timeframe.

### Rectification and erasure

You may request Teads the rectification of inaccurate personal data concerning you, as well as the completion of incomplete personal data. You may also request Teads to erase without undue delay your personal data when it is no longer necessary for Teads to retain such data.

### Portability

Upon request, Teads will provide you with the personal data you that provided to us and, if possible, will communicate this information directly to another data controller of your choice in a portable format when the processing is based on consent or contract.

6\. Data Security and Retention
-------------------------------

The security of your information is fundamental to Teads. We have implemented industry standard security measures, which include the use of firewalls and encryption to protect your personal information. If you have questions about the security of your personal information, you may contact us at [dpo@teads.com](mailto:dpo@teads.com).

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

7\. Transfer of Information to the U.S. and Other Countries
-----------------------------------------------------------

Teads is based in Amsterdam and we process and store information throughout the United States, Europe, Latin America, and Asia. Therefore, we and our service providers may transfer your information to, or store or access it in, jurisdictions that may not provide equivalent levels of data protection as your home jurisdiction.

In this context, please note that Teads may transfer your personal information outside the European Union as part of its processing. In such case the organization receiving your personal information will have provided to Teads adequate safeguards such as adherence to the EU Privacy Shield Framework, execution of the EU Standard Contractual Clauses for transfer to third countries, or another specifically stated lawful basis for the transfer of personal information to a third country.

8\. Privacy Policies of Third Parties
-------------------------------------

Our site includes links to other websites whose privacy practices may differ from ours. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy statements. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy statement of any website you visit.

9\. Choices for Access, Deletion, Opt-Out of Sale, and Right to Non-Discrimination for California.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

If you are a California resident, you have the right to know what personal information we collect, disclose, and “sell” about you (as that term is used in the CCPA). Additionally, you have the right to access, delete and opt-out from the “sale” of your personal information.

To exercise these rights, please follow the instructions below:

* **How to Request Access to Personal Information:** You may request access to your personal information twice in a 12-month period. To do so, please, email us at [dpo@teads.](mailto:dpo@teads.com)[com](mailto:dpo@teads.com). US residents can as well call us at 1-866-467-8688 (1-866-I-OPT-OUT). When being prompted, please use the code 777#. Account holders can request access to their personal information at any time by logging into their accounts on the Services. In response, we will produce an Access Report detailing the personal information we have collected, disclosed, and/or sold about you. This Access Report will be delivered by mail or electronically at your request in a reasonable timeframe.
* **How to Request Deletion of Personal Information:** You may request that Teads delete the personal information it has collected and/or maintained about you. To do so, please email us at [dpo@teads.com](mailto:dpo@teads.com). US residents can as well call us at 1-866-467-8688 (1-866-I-OPT-OUT). When being prompted, please use the code 777#. Note, we may need to retain certain personal information as permitted by law, such as to complete the transaction for which the personal information was collected, provide a requested good or service, detect security incidents, protect against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent or illegal activities, comply with legal obligations or to enable solely internal uses that are reasonably aligned with your expectations or lawful within the context in which you provided the information.
* **How to Opt-Out of the Sale of Personal Information:** We offer an opt-out from the use of cookies and other tracking technologies in connection with our Services, which may in some cases constitute the sale of your personal information under the CCPA or other privacy laws.  To opt-out of the sale of your personal information, please click [**Do Not Sell My Personal Information**](https://www.youronlinechoices.com/uk/your-ad-choices) or follow the browser setting instructions below. This will cause information to cease to be added to any cookies or other tracking technologies that have been set on our Services or block them entirely.  Please note that you will need to opt out again if you visit one of our Services from a different device or browser of if you clear your cookies.     

### Verification

Please note, we will take steps to verify your identity before fulfilling any consumer request. If you maintain an account with us, we will verify your identity through existing authentication practices for the account (e.g., login and password). If you are not a registered user, we will verify your identity by matching two or three data points that you provide with data points that we maintain and have determined to be reliable for the purposes of verification (e.g., browser and device ID). 

### Authorized Agents

You can use an authorized agent to make such requests on your behalf. But we may require the agent to provide a written permission and verify his/her identity or demonstrate that he or she has power of attorney. 

### Anti-Discrimination Right.

You have the right to be free from discrimination in product quality, goods or services if you choose to exercise your privacy rights under the CCPA. 

### Do Not Track Signals

Do Not Track is a privacy preference that users can set in their web browsers. When a user turns on the Do Not Track signal, the browser sends a message to websites requesting them not to track the user. At this time, we stop running targeted advertising in response to web browser “do not track” signals or other mechanisms. For information about Do Not Track, visit [www.allaboutdnt.org](http://www.allaboutdnt.org/). Please remove the paragraph

10\. Children’s Privacy
-----------------------

Our Services are not directed to children under the age of sixteen (16) in the United States or children under the age of legal majority in jurisdictions outside the United States, nor do we market products or services to such children.

11\. Teads Commitments
----------------------

Teads collects and uses data in accordance with all applicable laws and regulations, including but not limited to laws governing privacy and data protection.

12\. Contact Us
---------------

Teads is the data controller and our Data Protection Officer can be contacted for any question on this privacy policy by email or mail:

* By email: [dpo@teads.com](mailto:dpo@teads.com) or,
* By mail: DPO-Teads – 97 rue du cherche midi- 75006 Paris – France.
* You may also lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority, for instance in France: CNIL ([www.cnil.fr](about:blank)).
* For CCPA Purposes: As described in Section 9 above.

Advertisers
-----------

### Launch a campaign with us

Whether you have branding or performance objectives, Teads can help you deliver on your goals. Let’s talk about what we can do together.

Publishers
----------

### Join The Global Media Platform

Unlock incremental revenue from  
premium advertisers through ad experiences  
that respect your users.

Privacy

My Cookie Setting

For Advertisers

For Publishers

About Teads

Let us keep you informed  
of our latest news

Copyright 2024 - Made with in Montpellier

Come join an award-winning team

We and our partners use cookies on our website to give you the most relevant experience by remembering your preferences, analyzing site usage and enhancing site navigation. By clicking “Accept”, you consent to the storing of cookies on your device for these purposes. [More information](https://www.teads.com/teads-website-privacy-policy/)

Cookie preferencesACCEPTREJECT ALL

My Cookie Setting

Close

#### Privacy Overview

This website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may affect your browsing experience.

Necessary

 Necessary

Always Enabled

Necessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. These cookies ensure basic functionalities and security features of the website, anonymously.

| Cookie | Duration | Description |
| --- | --- | --- |
| cookielawinfo-checbox-analytics | 11 months | This cookie is set by GDPR Cookie Consent plugin. The cookie is used to store the user consent for the cookies in the category "Analytics". |
| cookielawinfo-checkbox-necessary | 11 months | This cookie is set by GDPR Cookie Consent plugin. The cookies is used to store the user consent for the cookies in the category "Necessary". |
| viewed\_cookie\_policy | 11 months | The cookie is set by the GDPR Cookie Consent plugin and is used to store whether or not user has consented to the use of cookies. It does not store any personal data. |

Analytics

 Analytics

Analytical cookies are used to understand how visitors interact with the website. These cookies help provide information on metrics the number of visitors, bounce rate, traffic source, etc.

| Cookie | Duration | Description |
| --- | --- | --- |
| \_\_hssc | 30 minutes | Cookie is placed by HubSpot. This cookie keeps track of sessions. This is used to determine if HubSpot should increment the session number and timestamps in the \_\_hstc cookie. It contains the domain, viewCount (increments each pageView in a session), and session start timestamp. |
| \_\_hssrc | It expires at the end of the session. | Cookie is placed by HubSpot. Whenever HubSpot changes the session cookie, this cookie is also set to determine if the visitor has restarted their browser. If this cookie does not exist when HubSpot manages cookies, it is considered a new session.It contains the value "1" when present. It expires at the end of the session. |
| \_\_hstc | 13 months | Cookie is placed by HubSpot. This cookie keeps track visitors. It contains the domain, utk, initial timestamp (first visit), last timestamp (last visit), current timestamp (this visit), and session number (increments for each subsequent session). |
| \_fbp | 3 months | Cookie is placed by Facebook to store and track visits across websites. |
| fr  | 3 months | Cookie is placed by Facebook to Enable ad delivery or retargeting. |
| hubspotutk | 13 months | Cookie is placed by HubSpot. This cookie keeps track of a visitor's identity. It is passed to HubSpot on form submission and used when deduplicating contacts. It contains an opaque GUID to represent the current visitor. |
| Teads Pixel |     | Teads pixel is placed by Teads to store and track visits across our website. |

SAVE & ACCEPT

Teads and Outbrain Merge To Form Leading Omnichannel Advertising Platform…
